[Music]
When they saw that he was going to give them a test, he gave us a test.
We shouldn't be in front of these people,
Captain.  [Music]
This vault is
made of the world's strongest titanium metal.
Their task was to open it.
You can use any of this equipment you want
.  [Music]
But you have time.
Just two minutes.
Your time starts
now
[music]
Ya
[music] There's only one more minute,
take the Explore Sticks
[music]
Cook Cook Master, are you decorating for the Ayudha Puja
?
Non-Storytelling
[Music]
You have the same rules and regulations
here, you can use whatever you want.
Time starts running
[Music]
Don't be a condom
technology
[Music] to use it
[Music] [
Music]
Stitch took two of them to use,
I came
[Music]
Now you know why they are
necessary for us, give them the necessary training
[Music] S
[Music]
Hello everyone, I have a
problem. I also like to do whatever the Budichavas
like
.  I thought the same way, and you
thought the same way. I was wrong.
I'll pick up that twig. I'll
tell you what my plan is. Listen, you idiots. A
lion or a sparrow
can't do anything in that place.  We need to get it from there and
bring it to a comfortable place for us.
That rich guy might
be a big troublemaker in Chennai today.  But the business he
started in our area, Pandi, is
still here
.  He will come to Pondicherry for two days
.  When he enters the dungeon,
he has a bunk.
I'm laying eggs in his car 200 meters before that stake.   Wait
a minute, Pandi. I'm beating
Pandi's egg.
Did you beat the egg in the car?  He
would call the manager from the gas station next to the car wash anyway.
I'll go there instead of that punk guy
.  Instead of water, I'll take gasoline and
fill the car with gasoline, saying that I'm going to refuel it
.  Okay,
my friend works at that branch
.  I come in as the guy who works there, pour
gasoline instead of water, and
touch the floor.   I'll
put petrol in that car in 10 minutes.  I'll
burn that car down inside.  What a
fool he is, he is so lazy.
This guy and I are doing it together.  We are getting tired and
fattening up that cart.  No one will have any
doubts about us.
I understand, Pandi and I will
do it together.   He and
his men jumped out of the burning car and
ran away.  Then
I'll pick up the pieces if he beats up his men and grows up
.  This is a bit
risky.  That's why I
do it alone.
How many people were there, Pandi?  I'm
hitting you, Pandi.
No, that's a risk.  I
will take care of them myself.  Pandi, don't worry about that
.  No matter how many people he has
, I'll
beat them.  Then
I lock a cheeky scythe in my hand, which is growing and growing, to come alone
.  I'm going to ask around, I wonder what's going on
.
I'll stab myself with a knife.
That cheeky bastard can't be killed.
Only a lock can do it.  I'm
stalking him from behind.  You
punch him from behind.  What kind of
gun is that?  I don't know what gun I'm looking for. I'll
tell you tomorrow.
Hi, brother, he
told me to give it to you.
I knew immediately when I saw who was the waste of yours, "Hey, Boda Kamachi."  This is the latest
technology and it's like, "
Hey, I'm going, I'm going, please."
Say you have to focus.
Hey, shut up for a while.  Okay, please, please,
I'm thinking of a drink too
.   If you tell me to
kill you, they're playing games
[Music]
Ah, the past will chase you and chase you, and keep pressing yourself,
pressing yourself, pressing yourself,
all the sins you committed yesterday will come
looking for you and one day they'll kill you,
simple simple life [Music] If someone
takes you one way, one day you won't remember,
someone will end you, I'll
give Bluetooth to everyone, we need to be connected to each other, everyone, everyone,
remember what I said, no matter what happens,
tell me, okay, we all brought it by hand, the
bag is a little big,
how are
you doing, I'll talk to all of us, no
one will talk, I'll
tell the brother I asked, enough, I'm
scared of this,
give it to me, hey,
this isn't a Bluetooth gimmick, it's not a made inferno, come and listen, come on, you idiot, put a headset on the ear that doesn't listen, I'm talking to the ear that doesn't listen, put a pill in the ear to
drink the pill,
I'm talking
I know you're joking.
Hey, the car is back from the main road.
Hurry up.   Brother, I'm
leaving now.  Hey,
get ready quickly.
Hey, brother, something fishy.
Someone parks their bike in the middle of the road and
falls asleep.  Hey, aren't you
Amsiya? Amsiya
is driving in a modern costume.  Hey, she
went upstairs and got a ten.  Munawata is not a man,
triple sum, hey, there's some other plan going on that we don't know about,
alert.  Hey, you
go away,
look at what's happening,
accident
[music]
[distress]
What, who's that?   The doll and
the baby are lying there, lying down,
lifting the baby into the cart, and putting
the cart on top of the
doll,
brother, why are you putting that box aside? Brother, the cart is coming, the cart is coming, over and over, who is
talking,
no one will come on the line, just
do something, okay, Pandi,
I'll take care of it.
Yo, Totha, I
told you not to add to this madness.
Yo, if you
leave on Sunday,
where are you going? [Music]
Hey, what's going on? Do you think you can come to our area,
beat up our people and run away?
That won't
happen as long as we're in this place.
Who is Rahul?
It's me, Rahul.
First, go and change the name.   The
old man drank it and then went over and over.
Hey, who is this? I have nothing to do with you.
Grandpa has escaped. He's not clean. Hey,
why is that dead body still burning? Hey,
Suriya, when you come, come here. Grandpa is clean. Hey, look over
there.
Why are you following me? The whole
family is crazy here. What's he doing here
now? Brother, are you stupid?
Hey,
sir. You're the one who belongs to us.
Hurry up.
Okay,
where are those apples and pears? I don't know
where they went. I
don't know where they went.  What
is the only mystery?  He came as if he
knew in advance how to beat an egg
.
Over and over, day by day, stay, stay.
Hey, if he escapes somehow, only his head will
run away.
Something is going wrong here.  Hey, wait,
hurry up, hurry up, come on
[Laughter] It
's nice to see you running away.   I will
shoot you dead just like this, for this fake
.
What's the matter, you old
woman?
You must have been chasing someone.
All those people
came to our house and tied up our children, including me
.   Look,
the second line is coming, take that too.
Hello, I told my mother something in Kovatham
.  This time,
baby, I love you,
father. Baby, I love you.
Hey, I'll talk about my baby
.   If
my brother said it, it would make sense. I'm
sorry to hear that.
Mansur, you
may have been a villain from the beginning.  But now I'm the
villain here.
Why are you running away at such an old age? Just do
one thing, put this gun away and
go to the top.  As long as you
are here, nothing will happen to me, I
will not let you go without killing me.
Good man [Music] Who is here, who is there, good man? Act
like a good man and go somewhere else. I don't know if he has gone away. Bad
man. Who is here, who is there, bad man? The one who has gathered to
beat you up. Will you beat me up? Will you
give me my wish?
Or break me? Go to the
auto that
you drove, go and run. [Singing] Go to the auto that you drove, go and run.
[Music] Will
I come, come, come, chase you? Will you return it to you in a
way that you have done wrong? Will you come,
come, touch you? Will you return it to you in a way that you have done wrong?
Where is he? He is hiding and
seems to be hiding. Why are you such a big
rowdy? What is my waste to you? Rahul
Moonji
This is Moonji, not this is Moonji, Moodevi Moonji,
where did you leave Moocha?
What are you doing, boys?
I'm hitting a full bottle.   It's
like a very scary Stranga
.  I know I'm going to faint, I
know I'm going to faint.
I fainted and died.
Killing death.
Oh,
Rahul, I'll go and get them
.  Stopped.
Okay.
What are you suspicious of?  I see.
Who will fly the car now?  Many leaves.   Don't be idle
.  There's a knife in your hand,
take it.  He will do it.  [Laughter]
Remember well.  No stab in the chest,
I'll ask myself, Dad, if I stab you in the chest, will you die
immediately? If I stab you in the neck,
you speak, we'll die.
Okay,
then go and stab me in the chest. Okay, come on,
okay, ready, the car, the
car,
hey, the car is gone.
Hey,
sir, the car, what are you doing now,
my car is gone?
My car,
he pushed the subject wheel
out of the classroom, sir.   He
twisted Dr. Kalidas's hand and
asked him to admit a suicide case without filling out the admission form.
He was the one who went on leave because he was afraid of that.
What is this roadblock?
How do I know, sir?  You know how to do it,
you have an answer for everything.  Hey,
do you know,
sir? Leave all that behind, sir.
Let's talk about Pasha Kannapin, sir.  Kassamo
is lazy, what's the point of being a
ghost?
That's another matter, sir.
Hey, leave it alone, sir. I'll dismiss him first,
sir.   For
a minute, that won't happen, that's wrong.
Why A?
What is the reason?  He came first in the entrance exam, whether he was asking questions
or talking nonsense
.  They
need a strong reason to dismiss him.
I [first] have got an idea.
Sir, prepare a difficult cost paper for the upcoming exam
.
I am asking a question from Silapathikaran Kundala Kesi Seevaka Chinthamani.  Honestly,
he will fail.
I'm serious, I'm noting,
oh, prepare the cost paper so much that no one can answer it
.  He ca
n't answer.  He will fail and I
will dispose in the next minutes.  Great
idea,
great [laughter] idea,
Rajara Rajara, the tax collectors are bringing the construction,
what to do,
what language do you speak,
sir? The tax collectors are
bringing the construction, where is the
ship going?
Why not?  I'm worried. Did you see the paper?
Yes, sir. Did you see it? In the paper
bandh, seven people in one family died by
cutting each other.
But it's not a big deal. Kuppamma
adjusted in Kanchipuram and gave birth to
seven children in one delivery.
What do you know from this? Why are you saying that God and the population
cannot be separated? Is it a
paper bag? Is it an English paper? Is it a
Hindu Express paper?
Peter,
what is Hindu Din's talk?
Have you been in the exam or have you been in the ticket
?  Is it
okay? We have ticked the fifth kostin.
You have to tick the
five.
Okay, the next one is six, mind is six. That's the Lord's
command. That's how it ends.
[Laughter] You have finished
the paper, thank you.
Okay, come on, I'll give it to you.   Is
n't it a difficult paper? That's what
I asked.
Wherever the learners go, special
Sri Rajaraman 95.5
Nice [Laughter]
All these rumblings, doctor,
hospital atmosphere, I'll think about it, what are the
words like
?
Do a postmortem on that outlaw.  You created the devil, uncle.
How happy I am to hear you say that you are a god [laughter].
Yes, I know this suitcase, what is this
locked case?  Sir, maybe this locked
suitcase is there.
Just sit there. I told you to set that cost
paper with difficulty. I did it.
Sir,
how? 95.5%?
I made a coin block. Did you make a shot and
pocket that coin?
Sir, only the carrom board
is there, please. Sir,
sir, how? He is on top
.  That's how I know sir,
sorry how do you know
[laughter] May I come
in sir, sir, did
you tell Mr. Rajarama to come?
We'll wait for you from now on.
Mr. Rajaram
Dean, I am [ __ ] myself.  Oh sir, will you bring varicose
veins? Sir, your people just shouted at you
.  Don't stay too long
.  Sit down.  I'm being yelled at
.
I sat there disrespectfully.  What habit is this?   It's
a habit you've been taught.
You stand in class and make us sit down and
teach us your lesson.
I'm talking about the same habit of following logic.  But if you
look at the marks you've bought, there's no logic to it.
I know very well that you did something wrong
.  I will never let
it go undiscovered, no matter what.  Why are you
posting a song? I'm
telling you openly. I made a pass after doing a promotion. What else will you have to
do? The
situation in the country is like this.
[Laughter]
What's wrong with being called a loser?
Hey,
I'm the one who called everyone a loser now.   It's just that now,
shut up, Mamu. No
one has ever spoken to me like this before
.  Everything needs a beginning,
Mama.  [Screaming] Mamu, what is that
Mamu, I'm telling you, meaning Mamu.  Now I am
Raja Raja Calling Raju.  So, my mother-in-law was calling, "Mamu,
that's it,
no cool down, cool down, cool down, what's the matter?" It
was like calling from home.
You don't know what's going on.  I thought I would
send you out of college.  Do you
remember when your mother sent you away from home? It was an
unforgettable day. I saw my father crying.
I have never seen him cry.
Even when my grandfather died, he stood still
like a stone. When you
said one word, "Sirukku," my eyes filled with tears.
I have
decided many things for my mother. Becoming a doctor is the next step for
you. You
can't take everything, big rice, put in and take.  Next to that, your
daughter asked for a bribe, right?
Next to that, she taught you a lesson. I
sang Krishna in a place where big men were. Uncle
shows me a stretcher. [Laughter]
I know what you're going to say. If
you tell me to get out and I go, it's
not respectful.  I have work to do.
I'm going.  You are a fool.  I have
urgent work.  What do you mean
[laughter]?  I
tell you myself.   The
poster
was put up by the builders. The
team was not allowed to
buy food from Palani and watched it from the bus. They didn't
pay attention.  It's all because
of you that I came here to finish it all and it
went in vain.  I did what I wanted.
Okay, what are you doing now?   Can you please
turn it over?   I'm not
hungry,
right? Count this 35 and
this 37. It's
not enough.
Then take 100, take 100. Why are you still
waiting? What's the matter?
We paid 100 rupees. There's no
discount. Don't you want to take 100 rupees? Let's go. It's
like you're bringing it here.
This is a line
bet. A person
said he wanted to eat 50 rupees and made a bet and
lost. Can
we come to the race?
Anyone can come except him.
What kind of bet is that
a person should eat 50 protons?  If
any of you eat it, I will
give you 100 rupees.   You
don't have to pay for Prota.  You're still
stuck, you have to give me ₹100
.  Why should you keep on giving birth to a child for a mother who has eaten a lot
?
50 Protava,
yes,
Naradi, is suffering from famine.
[Music] He miscalculated by looking at his figure
.  Good supplier,
four districts, two Poddanni,
against them, Dindigul district,
where is Prota, will they keep it until you come?
Go and take Prota, go
Hey, you ate 42, you
ate 50, you do
n't count the forts, you
ate 42, brother, I don't know, I don't know, I ate 50, I can't do it, you can't do it, you can't do it, I won't agree, I
ate, destroy all the forts,
I was the first to eat, you go and take it, you little one,
you go and build a fort,
what will we put in it?
Think well, the others will
come to all the halls.  How will he
get on stage? Now how will I get on stage? If you
know the house, tell me to put the names of four people in each
group. KP Mathiya, don't
jump on that building you mentioned.
[Music] [
Music]
Saras,
that's okay with me. [Music]
Okay, girl, turn around and look. [
Music]
Dad, who is that girl? She's like a ghost.
[Music]
What are you saying?  [Music]
No, really,
he said it was like a ghost.
That's all nothing.  Some
girl in the front has come wearing makeup like a ghost
.  I'll tell you that.  Hey,
this girl is a first-timer.
Who?  Me?
That's the father standing next to the house [music]
.
Papa?
[Music] Is
this girl okay with you?
Oh, you know this girl before
?
[Music]
[Screaming]
Love is
like a nail driven into a person's heart that he
will not forget on his deathbed.
[Music]
Who is that girl? [Music] She's like a ghost. She's
packing up and
saying, "Who is
that girl?" She's saying, "
No, she's doing whatever she wants."  Things have
n't been going well since this guy arrived.  He hasn't
spoken to me properly since yesterday.  [Music] Come here and don't
say another word.
That's all nothing.
No, dear.  I don't speak either.  [Music] Let Sarukka
speak whenever he feels like it.  Why is Priya
wearing makeup or
not? She looks perfect.  I'm
okay with it
[music]
They're letting our daughter go to hell like this right now.  How can we conceive a child while thinking of them
?
[Music]
Dad, please don't make me cry, leave me alone
.   What's going on? Nothing's going on.
My daughter is so upset that nothing's happening.
Who are you?  Who am I?
Who am I?  He's asking who I am right now
.  If we get married, that's it, we'll just
cut off our relationship completely.  No, no, no, that's
enough.
[Music]
This doesn't seem right to me [Music]
This is just a game, isn't it?
[Music] How can you tell the truth? Actually, in
this dress, you just look like an angel
[Music]
[Music] You
talk too much.